Is this how you treat the person
who saved your life?
Not even a thank you?
I didn't ask you to save me.
If you won't drink it, I will.
Only when you're full
do you have the strength
to face the world's challenges.
Haven't you disliked eggs
since you were little?
Who would eat this
if they could get
something high in calories?
What am I going to do with you?
I told you not to run off,
but you just had to.
Are you trying to get yourself killed,
or me?
When did you get this?
From a heartless woman.
It's none of your business.
You're a terrible swimmer.
Why risk your life to save me?
Your leg is perfectly fine.
Why pretend to be crippled?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Drop the act.
You staged the poisoning
and the fall into the lake.
A scheme to fake your death,
right?
When did you find out?
I'm just worried it's too dangerous.
If I just run away from the wedding,
it will implicate the whole Xue family.
But only if I die
will Ning Yuanci
spare my father and the others.
The fake death potion
we prepared last time
was accidentally knocked over
by Xue Keying.
This time,
there can't be any mistakes.
I've lost count of
how many times I've filmed
this drowning scene.
How could I not know
if it's true or false?
Don't think I'll obey your every word
just because you have leverage over me.
I risked my life to save you,
and you still don't believe me?
Now,
our fates
are tied together.
If you die,
I won't survive either.
I am not like you,
blessed with a birth mother's protection
and a father's love.
I faked my limp only to
avoid complex struggles
and live in peace.
But His Majesty
insisted on betrothing me to Ning Yuanci.
What choice did I have?
To live,
I had to die.
Only death
could offer an escape.
But have you ever thought
that if something goes wrong,
you would truly die?
Is there any other way?
Should I break the engagement
and drag down the entire Xue family?
Listen to me.
Do not use such extreme methods
to solve the problem.
I will help you find a way.
Your way
is nothing but pestering Ning Yuanci
until he marries you.
Yes, yes.
Ning Yuanci is the most charming man
in the world.
Such a fine man,
I must win him over myself.
I don't need anyone to yield him to me.
Trust me.
I will do everything I can
to make him agree to break the engagement.
If you don't believe me,
I will tell your parents
about your fake limp.
I heard you were on duty
in the backyard last night.
Did anyone see how Xue Ruowan
fell into the water?
I was originally going to
deliver calming tea to the Eldest Miss,
but when I arrived,
she was no longer in her room.
I was steaming jujube cakes,
which are the young ladies' favorite.
I have been guarding the stove
and watching the fire the whole time.
You are Xue Ruowan's personal maid.
So you were by her side
when she fell into the water.
Therefore,
you are the prime suspect.
That can't be.
Lan is a loyal servant.
It was the Second Miss who pushed her.
I saw it with my own eyes.
What?
I helped you,
and you bite the hand that feeds you.
You wretched girl,
how dare you frame my Ying'er!
I'll tear your mouth apart!
The Eldest Miss and the Second Miss
have never gotten along.
Recently, because of
the Eldest Miss's marriage
to the General,
she has been threatening
and making things difficult for her.
The Second Miss even
put down the bamboo pole early.
This is clearly kicking her
while she's down.
I prepared the bamboo pole to save her.
How did you know
she would fall into the water?
I...
If I tell them
I transmigrated into a script,
they'll think I'm crazy.
If I spoil the fact that Xue Ruowan
orchestrated this,
Ning Yuanci definitely won't let her off.
What should I do?
I prepared the bamboo pole
because my sister has weak legs.
Just in case one day,
she accidentally falls in,
we'd be prepared.
Besides,
I went in to save her myself.
How could I be the one who harmed her?
That makes sense.
You were with me the whole time
before she fell in last night.
So,
it definitely couldn't have been you
who pushed her.
A man
and a woman alone late at night.
Shouldn't the General
give our Ying'er
an explanation?
Ying'er,
what exactly happened?
It's not what you think.
We just
bumped into each other
in the back garden last night.
Right?
The Second Lady yesterday
specifically asked me out.
She kept pestering me,
saying
she wouldn't marry anyone but me.
I had no choice but
to reject her.
When did I ever
say I wanted to marry you?
Ying'er,
don't you always say
you'll only
marry Ning Yuanci in this life?
I didn't.
I'm not.
Whoever says that again is a dog.
Mother understands you.
You're just
being shy.
I really didn't mean that.
This matter ends here.
Ultimately,
it is just a minor conflict
between the two sisters.
If anyone dares to breathe a word of this
and ruin the young ladies' reputations,
I will break your legs.
Yes.
Is anyone even
listening to me?
General!
The whole city knows
about your marriage to my Xue family.
Your wedding with Wan'er
has been postponed again and again.
You have to give me an explanation.
What kind of explanation do you want,
Duke?
I want the General
to hold an engagement banquet
at Jinming Pool.
It will be a good explanation
to the public.
I'm also doing this
for the sake of my daughters' reputations.
I beg the General
to agree to my request.
Ning Yuanci.
Why did you exaggerate?
Saying I'm pestering you?
I was just trying to help you
out of kindness.
But you,
you're really unpopular in the residence.
Are you that popular?
Even ghosts would stay away from you.
You clearly know who the real culprit is
regarding Xue Ruowan
jumping into the lake.
Why didn't you tell the truth?
Who knows?
I don't know.
When people lie,
their pulse quickens.
What exactly
are you hiding for Xue Ruowan?
Or is there something
about your Xue family...
an unspeakable secret.
You know
Xue Ruowan doesn't like you.
Why don't you break the engagement
instead of forcing her to marry you?
Are you
plotting something?
My plot is
to marry both of you.
The three of us will live together.
Take care. I won't see you out.
What are you thinking about, General?
Xue Keying used to obey
my every word.
It's really strange
that she suddenly drew a line with me.
And
Xue Shiyan's attitude.
He seems very eager
to marry Xue Ruowan off to me.
Do you suspect
he has an ulterior motive?
Last time,
the assassin who attacked Xue Ruowan
used the same sword as mine.
And
the hidden weapon used
is also commonly used
by Northern spies.
Do you think this is a coincidence?
But except for the inner quarters
of the Duke's estate,
which haven't been searched,
I have investigated every corner
inside and outside
the other courtyards.
I found nothing suspicious.
Xue Shiyan offered
to hold the engagement banquet
at Jinming Pool.
Then let him have his way.
I'd like to see
who dares to play tricks
right under my nose.